
Command
    az postgres flexible-server parameter set : Update the parameter of a flexible server.

Arguments
    --source            : Source of the configuration.
    --value -v          : Value of the configuration.

Resource Id Arguments
    --ids               : One or more resource IDs (space-delimited). It should be a complete
                          resource ID containing all information of 'Resource Id' arguments. You
                          should provide either --ids or other 'Resource Id' arguments.
    --name -n           : The name of the server configuration.
    --resource-group -g : Name of resource group. You can configure the default group using `az
                          configure --defaults group=<name>`.
    --server-name -s    : Name of the server. The name can contain only lowercase letters, numbers,
                          and the hyphen (-) character. Minimum 3 characters and maximum 63
                          characters.
    --subscription      : Name or ID of subscription. You can configure the default subscription
                          using `az account set -s NAME_OR_ID`.

Global Arguments
    --debug             : Increase logging verbosity to show all debug logs.
    --help -h           : Show this help message and exit.
    --only-show-errors  : Only show errors, suppressing warnings.
    --output -o         : Output format.  Allowed values: json, jsonc, none, table, tsv, yaml,
                          yamlc.  Default: json.
    --query             : JMESPath query string. See http://jmespath.org/ for more information and
                          examples.
    --verbose           : Increase logging verbosity. Use --debug for full debug logs.

Examples
    Set a new parameter value.
        az postgres flexible-server parameter set --resource-group testGroup --server-name
        servername --name parameterName --value parameterValue

    Set a parameter value to its default.
        az postgres flexible-server parameter set --resource-group testGroup --server-name
        servername --name parameterName

To search AI knowledge base for examples, use: az find "az postgres flexible-server parameter set"

